Southwest Folklore Center Cassette Recordings Collection, 1975-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- From my being, Lee, Fred Jr., 1991; Cactus Records, A division of HEP Productions, p1991; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From cover, "Dedication: To my lovely wife Ruth, to the beautiful State of Arizona, and to the men and women of Desert Storm who so valiently fought for the freedom of all mankind, which is A NEVER ENDING WAR!"... Beautiful Arizona (1:53) -- The Mogollon (3:39) -- The Canyon so grand (3:14) -- H.H. blues (4:10) -- In the land of the sand (2:00) -- Ruth, which way do we go (2:44) -- R-U-T-H (2:55) -- Fool enough to fall (3:04) -- When Leslie makes that old white fiddle ring (3:27) -- Sunset at Tucson (3:15) --.; SWF 93.13/C.1
- Son de Pascola, 1981; 1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file, "recorded at the 1981 Santa Maria (Summer) Fiesta at the 39th St. Yaqui Chruch, by Juan Rivera... Sold to W.H. Smith, who had a small regional arts store, by Riveria for $5.00"... Barrio Libre -- Son de Pascola --; SWF 93.15/C.1
- Interview with Celestino Fernañdez, Fernañdez, Celestino, 1993 June 1; June 1, 1993; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: "Interview with Celestino Fernañdez concerning his May, 1993, visit to the shrine of Jesús Malverde in Culiacán, Sinaloa, Mexico"...; SWF 93.18/C.1
- Songs composed by J. Alberto Sepúlveda, Los Halcones de Malverde, 1 sound casstee, analog; NOTES: All ten songs composed by J. Alberto Sepúlveda...Performed by Los Halcones de Malverde: Eligio Gonzalez and J. Alberto Sepúlveda...Apostol de Malverde -- Anima de Malverde -- El cheque -- Un Diez de Mayo -- Ya estan cantando los gallos -- La Carroza de Malverde -- Campesino -- El Jaguar -- Paloma azul -- El Cristero --; SWF 93.18/C.2
- Arizona Dance Hands: An evening at Li'l Abner's, Tucson, Arizona, Armstrong, Dean, 1993 May; May, 1993; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Insert contains information about individual performers and notes about the Arizona Dance Hands group... Performers include: Dean Armstrong; Rosemary Koshmider; Toni Clark; Edsel Smith; Sunny Spenser; and Earl Mock... Fiddle hoedown -- Blue eyes crying in the rain -- Sweet Georgia Brown medley -- Tumbleweeds -- Darktown Strutter Ball -- I can't stop loving you -- Twinkle, Twinkle, little star -- I want you to tell me -- I love you, but I don't want to hurt you -- Clarinet polka -- Mockingbird -- Your cheating heart -- Banjo solo -- T for Texas -- Stumbling -- I was satisfied -- Minnie the Mermaid -- I fall to pieces -- San Antone Rose -- Maiden's prayer -- White lightening -- Storms never last -- Silver dew on the blue grass tonight -- Banjo solo -- Key's in the mailbox -- Little rock get-away -- Soppin' the gravy -- Texas plains -- Just a closer walk with Thee -- Orange Blossom Special -- Yellow Rose of Texas --; SWF 93.24/C.1
- Collection of Sonoran corridos, Los Hermanos Leyva, 1975; [1975?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: On cover, "Recorded in a bar in Sonora"...Recorded by Paco Manzo Taylor around 1975 in La Misa, Sonora (S. of Hermosillo)"... In Spanish... More information available in file, 94.1/M.1... La Persecución de Villa -- Los Indios con Obregon -- Jésus Garcia Corrido -- Corrido de General Obregon -- Battle in Nogales -- La Tumba de Villa (norteño group) -- Corrido de Francisco Madero y Mondregon, assassinations -- La Tumba de Villa -- Death of Villa -- Carabina 30/30 --; SWF 94.1/C.1
- BBC Folk Routes, Gu-Achi Fiddlers, 1994 January 23; January 23, 1994; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: "Audio tape of Gu-Achi Fiddlers on BBC Folk "Routes" program, Sunday, January 23, 1994"...; SWF 94.7/C.1
- The Lonesome cowboy: Songs of the American West, White, John I., 1994; Chatham, N.J., JWI Productions, p1994; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: On cover, photograph of John White and his brothers, Wickenburg, Arizona, 1932... cover contains information about the songs and poems and biographical information about John I. White... Whoopee-ti-yi-yo -- Buffalo skinners -- The Railroad corral -- Great Grandad/Great Grandma -- The Tenderfoot -- When the work's all done this Fall -- The Grass of Uncle Sam -- The Chuck wagon -- The Strawberry roan -- The Zebra dun -- Spanish is the loving tongue -- The Little old sod shanty on the claim -- The Sierry Petes -- Windy Bill -- Bury me out on the prairie -- The Cowboy's dream -- The Cowboy's prayer --; SWF 94.9/C.1
- Interview with Otis Chidester: Garden of Gethsemane, Chidester, Otis, 1994 May 5; [May 5, 1994]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Otis Chidester about the Garden of Gethsemane...; SWF 94.11/C.1
- Summer Youth Art Program Awards, Wakefield Elementary School, 1994; [Tucson, Ariz. Summer, 1994]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Taping of Wakefield Elementary School Summer Youth Art Program Awards... Taped by Cynthia L. Vidaurri...; SWF 94.16/C.1
- El Corrido del Indio Victorio, Paz, Daniel "Chato", 1957-1960; [Tucson, Ariz.]; ca. 1957-1960; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Third generation dub... Recorded by James S. Griffith, 1957-1960... Sung by Daniel "Chato" Paz of Tucson, formerly of Silver City, N.M... El Corrido del Indian Victorio --; SWF 95.4/C.1
- Blue Sky Boys: Bill and Earl, Blue Sky Boys, Roanoke, Virginia, Copper Creek Records; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Blue Sky Boys: Bill and Earl Bollick... Farm and fun time favorites, vol. 2... Amazing grace -- Alabama -- Two little rose buds -- Hoplight ladies -- The B-I-B-L-E -- Sweetest mother -- I wish I had never seen sunshine -- Just a little talk with Jesus -- Unloved and unclaimed -- East Tennessee blues -- Beautiful -- Will you miss me? -- Nine pound hammer -- The Chapel in the hills -- Lonesome road blues -- Whispering hope -- Take me back to Tennessee -- This evening light -- Going around this world, baby mine -- Short life of trouble -- The Royal telephone -- Old Joe Clark --.; SWF 95.6/C.1
- [Selections], Tucson Festival Society, [Tucson, Ariz.]; 1 sound cassette, analog; Abstract: Tucson Festival Society recording. 2 Papago hymns and 4 songs.; SWF 95.7/C.1
- Caborca, Sonora, Mexico; 3 sound cassettes, analog, Mendez, Luis, Guadalupe Bracamonte, and Loreto Murrietta, NOTES: Performed by Luis Mendez, Guadalupe Bracamonte, and Loreto Murrietta... Recorded by David Fuller, Caborca, Sonora, March 1995... Tape 1 is master, Tape 2 and 3 are second generation masters. PARTIAL CONTENTS: Joaquin Murrieta -- El corrido del minero -- Corrido de caborca -- Corrido de caborca #2 -- Corrido de Kiansis -- Corrido del palomino -- El peon caminero -- Corrido de Leon Toral -- Los indios con Obregón -- Corrido de Padre Kino -- Corrido de Jacinto Zenobio -- Corrido de caborca #3 -- Corrido de caborca #4 -- Corrido de trincheras -- Corrido de Sonora [fragment] -- La tumba de un suicida -- Sonora querida.; SWF 95.8/C.1; SWF 95.8/C.2; SWF 95.8/C.3
- Navajo songs, 1992; Washington, D.C., Smithsonian/Folkways Recordings, pc1992; 1 cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded by Laura Boulton in 1933 and 1940 in Navajo settlements in Arizona and New Mexico. Yeibichei song: Talking God's song -- Yeibichei song: Calling God's song -- Yeibichei song -- Corn grinding song -- 6 sway songs -- 4 circle dance songs -- 5 circle dance songs -- 4 moccasin game songs: Ye''iitsoh song, Counter stick song, The People of Lukachukai, Pinyon Jay song -- Moccasion game song: Wildcat song -- Moccasin game song: Chickadee song -- Moccasin game song (in vocables) -- Moccasin game song: Cicada or locust song -- Moccasin game song: Antelope song -- Moccasin game song: Crow song --.; SWF 95.9/C.1
- 16 exitos con los inimitables Leones de Durango, Leones de Durango, Discos Halcon; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: 16 exitos con los inimitables Leones de Durango... De buena gana caminos de Michoacan -- Con las estrellas -- Mi cresencia -- La Cajita de oro -- Clavel de primavera -- El Verde pinito -- Dos mares de lagrimas -- Caminos de Michoacan -- Mananitas a Jesus Malverde (Gildo Garcia G.) -- Palabra de hombre -- Corrido a Ceferino Ojeda (Jose Mileon) -- Flor de capomo -- La Tumba sera el final -- Corrido a Jesus Malverde (Gildo Garcia G.) -- El Prieto crispin -- Estrella divina -- De buena gana --.; SWF 95.10/C.1
- Los Tiempos, Los Astros del Norte de Roman Benitez, 1995; Sinaloa, Mex., Produced by YAEL, 1995; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Los tiempos -- No volvere -- Recibi un aviso -- El contrabando de Juarez -- Eres mala -- El padrino de Culiacan -- Mujer ladina -- El narco licenciado -- Morena Morenita -- La Divinagarza --.; SWF 95.10/C.2
- Special Collaborations, Jim Smith and Friends, 1986; Jim Smith, c1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Performed by Scott Hetherington, Patrick Dugan, Tim Arroway, Susie Rough, Edward Creason, Patricia Merrell, Bleu Wilson, Sal Biondollo,Jr., Michael Martinovich, Rusty Atherton, Rob Binion,Jr., Walter Caldwell... Lyrics by Jim Smith... Start writing the epitaphs (performed by Hetherington) -- Rip-up in Red Rock (Dugan) -- Herald of the heavens (Arroway) -- Like the eagle (Rough) -- Nobody cryin' (Dugan) -- Who caused the tragedy (Creason) -- The last war (Merrell) -- Legend of Chuck Jason (Wilson) -- Passion for power (Biondollo,Jr.) -- What-the-hell blues (Martinovich) -- Tucson (Atherton) -- Shoot out in Old Tucson (Creason) -- Rodeo rider (Binion,Jr.) -San Xavier del Bac I (Wilson) -- San Xavier del Bac II (Caldwell) --; SWF 95.21/C.1
- Around Arizona, Jim Smith and Friends, 1987; Jim Smith, c1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES:Performed by Cliff Collins, Scott Hetherington, Rusty Atherton, Ed Creason, Travis Edmonson, Rob Binion, Pat Dugan, Skip Wayne, Chris Cook, Larry Eby, Susie Rough, Freda Stevens, Cathy Eby... Arizona waltz (Collins) -- Phoenix-desert rose (Hetherington) -- Palo Verde - safe and sturdy (Hetherington) -- Tucson (Atherton) -- Shoot out in old Tucson (Creason) -- La vaquilla Colorado (Edmonson) -- Little Joe the wrangler (Edmonson) -- Rodeo rider (Binion) -- Rip-up in Red Rock (Dugan) -- A far far cry from home (Wayne) -- Had to go (Cook) -- Life (L.Eby) -- Start writing the epitaphs (Hetherington) -- They say she died (Hetherington) -- Try to live (Hetherington) -- Like the eagle (Rough) -- Something solid (Stevens) -- From Santa with love (C. Eby); SWF 95.21/C.2
- Orquesta Tipica de Sonora: Instituto Sonorense de Cultura, Orquesta Tipica de Sonora, 1990; Hermosillo, Sonora, Instituto Sonorense de Cultura, 1990; 1 cassette, analog; NOTES:Cassette cover explains the reason for the orquestra and what the music teaches (in spanish)... Performed by Orquesta Tipica de Sonora... Performers inculde: Rafael Alvarez, Contrabajo; José Tánor, violonchelo; Fernando Palma, violonchelo; Pedro Ramos, violin; Mario Alberto López, flauta; Rogelio de León, clarinete; Jorge Noé Zupo, trompeta; Horacio Lagarda Burgos, trombón... El Guaymense -- Rosas de la tarde -- Angelina -- El costeño -- Viva Morelia --La pilareña -- Mi desgracia -- Mujeres al hilo -- La chi...no...na -- Lila y Dalias -- La ley del tigre.; SWF 95.25/C.1
- Ten great New Mexican fiddlers, 1980-1995; “Field recordings of New Mexican Hispanic fiddlers, 1980-1995, collected by Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler, P.O. Box 4296, Albuquerque, NM 87196-4296”--Liner notes. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.1
- Recording of a visit with Elliott Johnson, Dec. 17, 1990, Santa Rosa, Ariz. [tape 1], Elliott Johnson, Lester Vavages, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, 1990 December 17; CONTENTS: [side A] Santa Rosa processional -- Squash fields -- Cuadrilla -- Big white tortilla -- Santa Rosa processional -- Sonora church two-step -- Pecosita/Juan Charrusqueado -- Waltz in two keys -- Memories in Ajo -- Chotis -- [side B] Pinto beans -- Madzuka [sic] -- Blackie’s -- Dawn chotis [?] -- Libby bird song -- Julia -- Moonlight -- Chotis -- El Quelite -- Mazurka. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.2
- Recording of a visit with Elliott Johnson, Dec. 17, 1990, Santa Rosa, Ariz. [tape 2], Elliott Johnson, Lester Vavages, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Cleofas Ortiz, 1990 December 17; CONTENTS: [side A] Caballito blanco (Cleofas Ortiz’s version) -- Caballito (Elliott Johnson’s version) -- Sopilote Matado -- Mazurka -- Mexican waltz (Guadalupe tune) -- Ali Oidak -- 2nd time San Xavier -- Peanut shoes -- 2 time waltz in A -- Mariachi Loco -- 2 ton polka (from Cleofas Ortiz) -- Polka Montana -- [side B] [Discussion] -- Chotis -- Polka -- Polka miercoles (Cleofas Ortiz) -- Home sweet home -- Cajun version of Home sweet home -- ending tune -- [Additional material from another tape]. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.3
- Elliott's Easter fiesta, Mar. 30-31, 1991, Elliott Johnson [et al.], 1991 March 30-31; CONTENTS: [side A] Cababi two-step -- Big white tortilla -- La capsula -- Curuque Chotis -- Processional -- Two-time waltz -- Blackie’s Polka -- Two ton polka -- Memories in Ajo -- Squash fields -- Sonora church -- Cuadrilla -- Elliott Johnson’s Caballito blanco -- [side B] Oak dale waltz -- Pecosita/Juan charrasqueado -- El ciego melquiades tune -- Libby bird song -- Gu-Achi mazurka -- Polka de Raffo -- Raffers reel -- Old California waltz -- Rainbow chotis -- Home sweet home. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.4
- Henry Johnson's memorial in Cababi, Ariz., May 26, 1991, Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Linda Askew, Scotty Mathis, 1991 May 26; CONTENTS: [side A] Moonlight chotis -- [?] -- Elliott Johnson’s caballito blanco -- Santa Rosa processional -- Octave chotis -- Pinto beans -- Perrodan two-step -- Valse de Escoba -- Two ton polka (Cleofas Ortiz)-- Two-time waltz -- [?] -- Cuadrilla de Pecos -- Italian tune -- Meringue -- Nellie’s morning bounce -- Cowboy waltz -- [side B] Happy one-step -- Johnny can’t dance -- Rabbit song -- Tecolote -- Libby bird song -- Mary Johnson’s -- Valse de Escobar (Henry) -- Moonlight chotis. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.5
- Interview with Elliott Johnson, Oct. 19, 1991, in Cababi, Ariz. [tape 1], Elliott Johnson, 1991 October 19; CONTENTS: [side A] It’s in there chotis -- Second time in San Xavier -- Cababi Polka -- Peanut shoes -- First choice -- Mary Johnson’s chotis -- Big shoes -- Santa Rosa processional -- St. Rose of Lima -- Two time waltz in A -- Moonlight chotis -- Squash fields -- Sonora church two-step -- [side B] Sonora church two-step (continued) -- Port Townsend quadrilla -- Libby bird song mazurka -- Blackie’s polka -- Great big white tortilla -- Pinto beans -- La capilla -- Caballito blanco -- Mazurka -- Mazurka harmony with Elliott -- March of the red shoes. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.6
- Interview with Elliott Johnson, Oct. 19, 1991, in Cababi, Ariz. [tape 2], Elliott Johnson, 1991 October 19; CONTENTS: [side A] Polka [?] -- Cisco band tune -- [?] -- [?] -- Mary Johnson’s chotis -- First choice -- [side B] Elliott Johnson discusses learning music and oral tradition. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.7
- Elliott Johnson in Cababi, Ariz., Dec. 19, 1991 [tape 1], Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Ira Gwin, 1991 December 19; CONTENTS: [side A] Cuadrilla -- Second time in San Xavier -- Mary Johnson’s -- Henry’s waltz -- Big shoes -- First choice -- Blackie’s -- Moonlight -- Big white tortilla -- Perrodan two-step -- [side B] Peanut shoes -- Mazurka -- St. Rose of Lima -- Rosita -- Tecolote -- Mary Johnson’s -- Caballito blanco -- Two-ton polka -- Two-time waltz in A -- Libby bird song -- Sonora church. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.8
- Elliott Johnson in Cababi, Ariz., Dec. 19, 1991 [tape 2], Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Ira Gwin, 1991 December 19; CONTENTS: [side A] Cuadrilla -- Second time in San Xavier -- Mary Johnson’s -- Henry’s waltz -- Big shoes -- First choice -- Blackie’s -- Moonlight -- Big white tortilla -- Perrodan two-step -- [side B] Peanut shoes -- Mazurka -- St. Rose of Lima -- Rosita -- Tecolote -- Mary Johnson’s -- Caballito blanco -- Two-ton polka -- Two-time waltz in A -- Libby bird song -- Sonora church. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.9
- Elliott Johnson in Cababi, Ariz., Dec. 19, 1991 [tape 3], Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Ira Gwin, 1991 December 19; CONTENTS: [side A] Polka [?] -- La cuna Vicente Aragon -- Red fox waltz -- Dawn chotis Dawn chotis -- Rosalle [?] de bon matin -- La bastrangue -- Valse de Soulard -- [side B] La cuna (Cleofas Ortiz) -- [Other cuna (Cleofas Ortiz)] -- Mi suegra (aprieta mis botas?) -- Camino al norte -- Cuadrilla de Pecos -- Mary Johnson’s Squash fields -- Home sweet home. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.10
- Elliott's band at Fred's Steak House, May 29-31, 1992 [tape 1], Elliott Johnson [et al.], 1992 May 29-31; CONTENTS: [side A] Flor Marchita -- Buenos Dias Paloma Blanca -- De Colores -- Sonora Church [?] -- [?] -- [?] -- [?] -- Libby Bord Song Mazurka -- Squash Fields -- Santa Rosa Processional -- Hohokam -- St. Rose of Lima -- Mary Johnson's -- Memories in Ajo -- Julia -- [side B] Hoodoo Boogie -- Eliott talking -- Marla Chotis -- St. Rose of Lima -- Ajo Orchestra Tune -- Big Shoes -- 2nd Time in San Xavier -- Meringue -- Corrido de Monterrey -- Polka in 2 keys -- La Capsula -- Squash Fields -- Pinto Beans -- Lonnie Polka -- Purple Lillies -- Hohokam -- Blackie's -- Mary Johnson's -- Peanut Shoes -- 1st Choice -- 2nd Time in San Xavier (with Ken K., Jeanie McL., Scott M, Lindo A, Jacquie Wohl, Craig Tinney, Paul Rangell, Sally Arbink [?]) Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.11
- Elliott's band at Fred's Steak House, May 29-31, 1992 [tape 2], Elliott Johnson [et al.], 1992 May 29-31; CONTENTS: [side A] Maria Chotis -- St. Rose of Lima -- 40's tune from Ajo Orchestra -- Big Shoes -- Dawn -- 2nd Time in San Xavier -- ? tune in 3 keys -- Meringue -- [side B] Meringue -- Corrido de Monterrey -- Polka in 2 keys -- La Capsula -- Squash Fields -- Purple Lillies -- Mary Johnson's Chotis -- Curlique (Peanut Shoes) -- 1st Choice. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.12
- Elliott Johnson in Cababi, Ariz., Sept. 25-26, 1992 [tape 1], Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Scott Mathis, Linda Askew, Emily Abbink, Rose Hutchinson, Jerry Loes, 1992 September 25-26; CONTENTS: [side A] Tune with Paul -- Henry's Waltz -- Big White Tortilla -- Cuadrilla -- Santa Rosa Processional -- Love Bride Waltz -- Texas -- Angel Matteas Tune -- Paul Whitesox -- [side B] Waltz - La Palma -- Polka Luz -- Magnolia -- Flor de Canela -- Haitien Tune -- Dawn -- Linda's Waltz Linda -- Libby Bird Song -- 2 time waltz in A -- Meringue. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.13
- Elliott Johnson in Cababi, Ariz., Sept. 25-26, 1992 [tape 2], Elliott Johnson, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Scott Mathis, Linda Askew, Emily Abbink, Rose Hutchinson, Jerry Loes, 1992 September 25-26; CONTENTS: [side A] Saint Rose of Lima -- Purple Lillies -- Big Shoes -- Blackie's -- Squash Fields -- 1st Choice [side B] Lonnie's -- Wild Rose of the mountain -- Italian Waltz -- Caballito Blanco -- Spreante Perdute [sic] -- Moonlight Chotis -- Sonora Church 2 step. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.14
- Elliott Johnson in Santa Rosa, Ariz., Dec. 17, 1992 [tape 1], Elliott Johnson [et al.?], 1992 December 17; CONTENTS: [side A] Paul's White Sox -- Biscuit Cheeks -- Lonnie's -- 2 time Waltz -- Corrido de Monterrey -- 2nd Time in San Xavier -- Doodlings -- 1st Choice -- Doodlings -- -- SIDE B -- Big White Tortilla -- Flop Eared Chotis -- From Alex Gomes -- [?] chotis -- F chotis -- Cuadrilla in 2 keys -- Mary Johnson's -- Kotis [sic] -- Card by ganglat [!?] -- Wild Rose of the Mountain -- Texas -- Henry's Waltz. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.15
- Elliott Johnson in Santa Rosa, Ariz., Dec. 17, 1992 [tape 2], Elliott Johnson [et al.?], 1992 December 17; CONTENTS: [side A] Swedish Walking Tune -- Chicken Reel -- St. Rose of Lima -- Purple Lillies -- Valse a Reed -- Squash Fields -- Minor Tease -- Santa Rosalia -- Caballito Blanco -- Dm. Cuadrilla -- Cuadrilla de Pecos -- A-E Jig -- [side B] -- Perrodan 2-step -- Blackie's -- Elliott Hambo -- Pascola Tune -- Montañeses de Alamo tune -- Moonlight -- Maria's. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.16
- Radio France performance of Elliott Johnson's music, July 22, 1995, Ken Keppeler, Jeanie McLerie, Linda Askew, Scott Mathis, 1995 July 22; Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.17
- Memories in Cababi (c1995, UBIK Sound #UB27), Bayou Eclectico [i.e., Bayou Seco], CONTENTS: [side 1]Cuadrilla -- Biscuit cheeks -- Big shoes -- Caballito blanco -- Squash fields -- Cababi polka/Hohokam polka -- Sonora church two-step -- [side 2] First choice -- Great big white tortillas -- Dawn/High note -- Pinto beans -- Mary Johnson’s/Blackie’s -- Peanut shoes -- Memories in Ajo. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.18
- Memories in Cababi (c1995, UBIK Sound #UB27), Bayou Eclectico [i.e., Bayou Seco], Duplicate of SWF 97.19/C.18 CONTENTS: [side 1]Cuadrilla -- Biscuit cheeks -- Big shoes -- Caballito blanco -- Squash fields -- Cababi polka/Hohokam polka -- Sonora church two-step -- [side 2] First choice -- Great big white tortillas -- Dawn/High note -- Pinto beans -- Mary Johnson’s/Blackie’s -- Peanut shoes -- Memories in Ajo. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.19
- Following in the tuneprints (c1995, UBIK Sound #UB25), Bayou Seco, CONTENTS: [side 1] Valse a Mexico/Old fashioned two-step -- Un soir -- Same old moon -- First choice/Two-step -- Rio Frio medley -- Palomita que vienes herida/Goosen -- Flor de las flores -- Polka Malibuski -- Lonesome cowgirl’s blues -- [side 2] Caballo bronco/La favorita -- Valse a Ballot -- La Vaquera/Valse a vachers -- Elliott’s special -- Mary Johnson’s chotis/Blackie’s polka -- Fleurs de la jeunesse -- Canray’s Copenhagen -- Mad cowboy love. Source: Jeanie McLerie and Ken Keppeler; SWF 97.19/C.20
- Lalo Guerrero canta musica romantica, Lalo Guerrero, CONTENTS: [side 1] Valse a Mexico/Old fashioned two-step -- Un soir -- Same old moon -- First choice/Two-step -- Rio Frio medley -- Palomita que vienes herida/Goosen -- Flor de las flores -- Polka Malibuski -- Lonesome cowgirl’s blues -- [side 2] Caballo bronco/La favorita -- Valse a Ballot -- La Vaquera/Valse a vachers -- Elliott’s special -- Mary Johnson’s chotis/Blackie’s polka -- Fleurs de la jeunesse -- Canray’s Copenhagen -- Mad cowboy love. Source: Lalo Guerrero; SWF 97.19/C.20
- Lalo Guerrero canta musica romantica, Lalo Guerrero, CONTENTS: [side A] Florecita -- Despierta Corazón -- Soñando Esperaré -- Enamorado -- Separación -- La Canción de los Dos -- Aquella Vez -- El Aventurero -- No Llores -- Así te Quiero Ver -- En Ti -- Flor Deshojada -- Tu Vendrás a Buscarme -- Si no Vuelves -- Prisionero -- Milliones de Mujeres -- No te Aflijes Morena -- Dos Almas y un Corazón -- Vengo a Pedirte -- [side B] Hipocrita -- El Desaventurado -- Eso Quisimos -- Convencete -- Ya no Puedo Quererte -- Quien Será mi Rival -- Sufre como Sufre -- Mia -- Acuérdate de Mi -- Yo Sé que es Imposible -- Llorar -- Llegaste Tarde -- El Alacrán -- La Media Naranja -- Cosita Linda. Source: Lalo Guerrero; SWF 97.21/C.1
- Lalo Guerrero canta tropical 60's, Lalo Guerrero, CONTENTS: [side A] -- Manzanita -- Mambo Mambo -- Mambito -- Mambo Guajiro -- Mambo Numero Zero -- Para Para la Rumba -- Montuno -- Contestación a la Casa -- Mentira -- Flor Deshojada -- Pecadora -- El Aventurero -- No Me Vuelvo a Enamorar -- Soñando Esperaré -- Sufre Como Sufro -- En Ti -- Vuelvame a Besar -- Quien Será mi Rival -- Así te quiero Ver -- Se Llama Lupe -- Elena -- Yo Soy el Bato -- El Hombre Gordo -- Se Fué y me Dejó. Source: Lalo Guerrero; SWF 97.21/C.2